palminfocenter.com 2004-06-04

# PalmInfocenter.com: Privacy Statement

**PalmInfocenter Privacy Statement**   
**_Registration_**  
We will **NOT** sell, share or redistribute your email address for any reason without your prior consent. 

In order to use some features of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as age and gender), but is encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. This information is displayed in the user's public profile and can be viewed by all visitors of this Web site. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online this information is available to the public and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. We've taken steps to reduce spam by requreing that only logged in registered users can view public profiles. 

**_Public Forums_**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**_Cookies_**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will have to manually type in their password each time they want to access a password protected feature. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

**_Third-Party Advertising_**  
We sometimes use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1x1 pixel .gif technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. 

**_Opt-Out_**  
If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies. 

**_Log Files_**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user's actions on our Web site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**_Links_**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that PalmInfocenter.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**_Polls & Contests_**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these polls or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Poll results are not linked to personally identifiable information. Results will only be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

Any privacy policy questions or concerns can be addressed to the [Editor](mailto:webmaster@palminfocenter.com).
